traveldealsfinder.com 2012-10-20

# Privacy Policy - Travel Deals 2012

Your Privacy  
We give our site visitors the opportunity to provide Traveldealsfinder.com with their personal information in response to specific services or tasks (e.g., signing up for our newsletters). In order to receive additional services, visitors may be required to provide personal information such as an email address.

Email Privacy  
Traveldealsfinder.com does not send unsolicited emails. Users who wish to unsubscribe from any mailing list may click the “unsubscribe” link within the email text. Or, the User may email support@Traveldealsfinder.com with the name and address of the emails the User would like to unsubscribe from.

Traveldealsfinder.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission. We comply fully with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. If at any time you would like to opt-out of our communications, please contact help@Traveldealsfinder.com.

Minors  
Traveldealsfinder.com does not seek to target Users under the age of 13. Any Users of the Site under the age of 13 should be acting under the supervision of a parent or guardian.

Cookies  
Traveldealsfinder.com uses cookies for aggregate tracking purposes. Our merchant partners may use cookies and similar means to collect aggregate statistical information. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

Intellectual Property, Privacy and Publicity  
The trademarks, logos and service marks displayed on the site are either the registered or unregistered trademarks of each offer site’s parent entity or are used under license. Everything you see or read on the site is copyrighted unless otherwise noted and may not be used or reproduced in any form.

Confidentiality  
Please do not send to Traveldealsfinder.com or post on Traveldealsfinder.com anything that constitutes a trade secret, confidential or proprietary information. We are not in a position to accept such information, nor can we agree to obligations of nondisclosure or confidentiality with regard to submitted plans or ideas. You agree that any information or materials that you, or individuals acting on your behalf, provide to any Traveldealsfinder.com channel will not be considered confidential or proprietary.

Revisions  
Traveldealsfinder.com may at any time revise the terms and conditions herein by updating this legal page. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the current terms and conditions.

### Privacy Policy : Online Booking, Feedback, Comments and Reviews

Check this section for latest comments, reviews and feedback on Privacy Policy
